{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165474105","data":{"timestamp":" 947165474105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165486423","data":{"timestamp":" 947165486423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165490509","data":{"timestamp":" 947165490509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165494374","data":{"timestamp":" 947165494374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165498214","data":{"timestamp":" 947165498213"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165530960","data":{"timestamp":" 947165530960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165535379","data":{"timestamp":" 947165535379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165550136","data":{"timestamp":" 947165550136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165556504","data":{"timestamp":" 947165556504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165559927","data":{"timestamp":" 947165559927"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165577895","data":{"timestamp":" 947165577895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165582502","data":{"timestamp":" 947165582501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165586222","data":{"timestamp":" 947165586222"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165596586","data":{"timestamp":" 947165596586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165605306","data":{"timestamp":" 947165605306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165609257","data":{"timestamp":" 947165609257"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165627524","data":{"timestamp":" 947165627524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165633102","data":{"timestamp":" 947165633102"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165640828","data":{"timestamp":" 947165640828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165648236","data":{"timestamp":" 947165648236"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165653524","data":{"timestamp":" 947165653524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165684234","data":{"timestamp":" 947165684234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165690766","data":{"timestamp":" 947165690766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165694394","data":{"timestamp":" 947165694394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165700165","data":{"timestamp":" 947165700165"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 533b3c83-2dd0-4df9-b4bb-ba0e5077638f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165735520","data":{"timestamp":" 947165735520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165739736","data":{"timestamp":" 947165739736"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165744200","data":{"timestamp":" 947165744200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165748034","data":{"timestamp":" 947165748034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165753843","data":{"timestamp":" 947165753843"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165757148","data":{"timestamp":" 947165757148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165760580","data":{"timestamp":" 947165760580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165764336","data":{"timestamp":" 947165764336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165768135","data":{"timestamp":" 947165768135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165772004","data":{"timestamp":" 947165772004"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165776177","data":{"timestamp":" 947165776177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165779679","data":{"timestamp":" 947165779678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165783622","data":{"timestamp":" 947165783621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165787378","data":{"timestamp":" 947165787378"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165790991","data":{"timestamp":" 947165790991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-g"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165796297","data":{"timestamp":" 947165796297"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165800736","data":{"timestamp":" 947165800736"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165855046","data":{"timestamp":" 947165855046"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_l-i-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165876310","data":{"timestamp":" 947165876309"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_f-r-t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165881523","data":{"timestamp":" 947165881523"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165895530","data":{"timestamp":" 947165895530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-u-y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165900412","data":{"timestamp":" 947165900412"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165941436","data":{"timestamp":" 947165941436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-v-u"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165959634","data":{"timestamp":" 947165959634"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165965433","data":{"timestamp":" 947165965432"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 6dafc7a2-2ea3-4538-8205-1bace8f5bd9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947165998707","data":{"timestamp":" 947165998707"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 7d2af7e4-be0d-4cf1-813b-d3d71a1d4250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166001996","data":{"timestamp":" 947166001995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 7d2af7e4-be0d-4cf1-813b-d3d71a1d4250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166011253","data":{"timestamp":" 947166011253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 7d2af7e4-be0d-4cf1-813b-d3d71a1d4250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166018918","data":{"timestamp":" 947166018918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 7d2af7e4-be0d-4cf1-813b-d3d71a1d4250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166026073","data":{"timestamp":" 947166026073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 7d2af7e4-be0d-4cf1-813b-d3d71a1d4250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166028091","data":{"timestamp":" 947166028090"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 7d2af7e4-be0d-4cf1-813b-d3d71a1d4250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166055936","data":{"timestamp":" 947166055935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 7d2af7e4-be0d-4cf1-813b-d3d71a1d4250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166068448","data":{"timestamp":" 947166068448"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 7d2af7e4-be0d-4cf1-813b-d3d71a1d4250"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166126418","data":{"timestamp":" 947166126417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 720af9f4-7868-4455-b580-294d9df6be10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166128900","data":{"timestamp":" 947166128900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 720af9f4-7868-4455-b580-294d9df6be10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166130502","data":{"timestamp":" 947166130501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 720af9f4-7868-4455-b580-294d9df6be10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ubao"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAO"," userResponse":" UBAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166135168","data":{"timestamp":" 947166135168"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 720af9f4-7868-4455-b580-294d9df6be10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ubao"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAO"," userResponse":" UBAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166136790","data":{"timestamp":" 947166136789"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 720af9f4-7868-4455-b580-294d9df6be10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" uzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZI"," userResponse":" UZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166140068","data":{"timestamp":" 947166140068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 720af9f4-7868-4455-b580-294d9df6be10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" uzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZI"," userResponse":" UZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166141691","data":{"timestamp":" 947166141690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 720af9f4-7868-4455-b580-294d9df6be10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" uyoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UYOGA"," userResponse":" UYOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166145689","data":{"timestamp":" 947166145688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 720af9f4-7868-4455-b580-294d9df6be10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" uyoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UYOGA"," userResponse":" UYOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166147304","data":{"timestamp":" 947166147303"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 720af9f4-7868-4455-b580-294d9df6be10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UA"," userResponse":" UA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166149775","data":{"timestamp":" 947166149774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 720af9f4-7868-4455-b580-294d9df6be10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UA"," userResponse":" UA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166151372","data":{"timestamp":" 947166151371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 720af9f4-7868-4455-b580-294d9df6be10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukuta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUTA"," userResponse":" UKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166155682","data":{"timestamp":" 947166155681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 720af9f4-7868-4455-b580-294d9df6be10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukuta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUTA"," userResponse":" UKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166157334","data":{"timestamp":" 947166157334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 720af9f4-7868-4455-b580-294d9df6be10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" udongo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDONGO"," userResponse":" UDONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166162216","data":{"timestamp":" 947166162216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 720af9f4-7868-4455-b580-294d9df6be10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" udongo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDONGO"," userResponse":" UDONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166163849","data":{"timestamp":" 947166163848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 720af9f4-7868-4455-b580-294d9df6be10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" UKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166167528","data":{"timestamp":" 947166167528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 720af9f4-7868-4455-b580-294d9df6be10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" UKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166169557","data":{"timestamp":" 947166169555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 720af9f4-7868-4455-b580-294d9df6be10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ukulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166169699","data":{"timestamp":" 947166169699"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 720af9f4-7868-4455-b580-294d9df6be10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" UKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166222674","data":{"timestamp":" 947166222673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 43ee4677-0a37-4f94-9343-0cfbc4a48d1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166233082","data":{"timestamp":" 947166233082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 43ee4677-0a37-4f94-9343-0cfbc4a48d1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166234721","data":{"timestamp":" 947166234720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 43ee4677-0a37-4f94-9343-0cfbc4a48d1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ubao"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAO"," userResponse":" UBAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166237922","data":{"timestamp":" 947166237921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 43ee4677-0a37-4f94-9343-0cfbc4a48d1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ubao"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAO"," userResponse":" UBAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166239521","data":{"timestamp":" 947166239520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 43ee4677-0a37-4f94-9343-0cfbc4a48d1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" uzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZI"," userResponse":" UZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166242269","data":{"timestamp":" 947166242268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 43ee4677-0a37-4f94-9343-0cfbc4a48d1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" uzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZI"," userResponse":" UZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166243869","data":{"timestamp":" 947166243868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 43ee4677-0a37-4f94-9343-0cfbc4a48d1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" uyoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UYOGA"," userResponse":" UYOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166247295","data":{"timestamp":" 947166247294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 43ee4677-0a37-4f94-9343-0cfbc4a48d1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" uyoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UYOGA"," userResponse":" UYOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166248917","data":{"timestamp":" 947166248917"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 43ee4677-0a37-4f94-9343-0cfbc4a48d1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UA"," userResponse":" UA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166252701","data":{"timestamp":" 947166252700"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 43ee4677-0a37-4f94-9343-0cfbc4a48d1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UA"," userResponse":" UA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166254323","data":{"timestamp":" 947166254322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 43ee4677-0a37-4f94-9343-0cfbc4a48d1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukuta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUTA"," userResponse":" UKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166257574","data":{"timestamp":" 947166257573"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 43ee4677-0a37-4f94-9343-0cfbc4a48d1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukuta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUTA"," userResponse":" UKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166259210","data":{"timestamp":" 947166259209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 43ee4677-0a37-4f94-9343-0cfbc4a48d1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" udongo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDONGO"," userResponse":" UDONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166262999","data":{"timestamp":" 947166262998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 43ee4677-0a37-4f94-9343-0cfbc4a48d1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" udongo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDONGO"," userResponse":" UDONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166264603","data":{"timestamp":" 947166264603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 43ee4677-0a37-4f94-9343-0cfbc4a48d1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" UKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166267751","data":{"timestamp":" 947166267750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 43ee4677-0a37-4f94-9343-0cfbc4a48d1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" UKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.59__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166269778","data":{"timestamp":" 947166269776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 43ee4677-0a37-4f94-9343-0cfbc4a48d1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ukulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947166269914","data":{"timestamp":" 947166269914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_163054"," gameId":" 43ee4677-0a37-4f94-9343-0cfbc4a48d1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.59__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ukulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" UKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}